https://peachweathers.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyOver 60 Years of Combined Experience Inpersonal injury LawPeach & Weathers Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used and shared when you visit or make a purchase at https://peachweathers.com.PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. In addition, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products you view, which websites or search terms indicate the Site and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this information automatically collected as "Information collected".We may collect information using the following technologies:- "Webforms", you may choose to provide us with your contact and personal information through any form of the website on our website. The purpose of sending your data is to express us your exclusive interest in our products or services. (More common)- "Cookies" are data files that are placed on your device or computer and generally include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.- "Log files" track actions that occur on the Site and collect data, including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, reference / exit pages, and timestamps.- "Web beacons", "tags" and "pixels" are electronic files used to record information about how you navigate the Site.- "Google Anaylitics" to collect (non-personal) data on site visitors- "Fastbase", we may use it to collect contact information and name of site visitors with regard to our business only.In addition, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect some of your information, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), e- mail address and phone number. We refer to this information as "Order Information".When we talk about "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, we are talking about Device Information, Information Collected, and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we generally collect to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging shipping, and providing invoices and / or order confirmations). In addition, we use this request information to: Communicate with you; Select our requests for potential risk or fraud; and When you agree to the preferences you have shared with us, provide information or publicity related to our products or services.We use the collected Information that we collect to help us identify potential risks and frauds (in particular, your IP address) and, more generally, to improve and optimize our Site (for example, generating analyzes of how our customers navigate and interact with Website and evaluate the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your personal information with third parties to help us use your personal information as described above. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how Google uses your personal information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also disable Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.We do not share or sell your personal information to any party that is outside the normal operation of our business under any circumstances.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal request for information that we receive, or to protect our rights.BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide targeted advertisements or marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you. For more information on how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work .You can disable targeted advertising by:
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https: // advertise .bingads.microsoft.com / en-US / resources / policies / personalized-adsIn addition, you can disable some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.NO TRACKING
Please note that we do not change the data collection and usage practices of our Site when we see a No Crawl signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access the personal information we hold about you and to request that your personal information be corrected, updated or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.In addition, if you are a European resident, we note that we are processing your information to comply with any agreements we may have with you (for example, if you place a request through the Site) or to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Also, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTION AND PROTECTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will keep your Order Information for our records, unless and until you ask us to exclude this information.We implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information.MINORS
The site is not intended for people under 18 years.CHANGING
We may update this privacy policy from time to time to reflect, for example, changes in our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions or would like to make a complaint, please contact us using the form on our contact page https://peachweathers.com/contact-peach-weathers/Policy Update Date: 5/30/2018
Have Questions?Contact us today for a free initial consultation.Name *
First
Last
Email *
PhoneBrief Description of Your Legal IssueConsent *Disclaimer: The use of the internet or this form for communication with the firm or any individual member of the firm does not establish an attorney-client relationship. Confidential or time-sensitive information should not be sent through this form. I Have Read The Disclaimer and Privacy Policy*CommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Redlands OfficeRiverside Office® 2020 By Peach & Weathers - A Law Corporation. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy | Disclaimer | Site Map
map-markertwitter-squarefacebook-squarelinkedin-squaremobileinstagram
